[Music]
[音乐]
okay I'm ready you ready thanks for
好吧，我准备好了，谢谢
coming so really great to see so many of
真的很高兴看到这么多
you at the end of the day I'm sure
在一天结束时你肯定
you're as tired as I am
你和我一样累
beer is coming
啤酒来了
don't worry I won't I won't keep you
别担心，我不会，我不会留住你
from your beer so I gave a talk at
从你的啤酒中，所以我在
spring i/o last year in in this room I
去年春天我在这个房间里
think which was about spring cloud
想想关于春天的云
function and the topic came up when I
功能和主题出现，当我
was working on springtime function about
正在从事春季功能
cold start time for the jvm the Java
Java的jvm的冷启动时间
processes just tend to take a little bit
流程往往需要一点时间
of time to get started
有时间开始
once they're started of course the JVM
一旦他们开始，当然是JVM
is an awesome place to run you know fast
是一个很棒的地方，让您快速了解
efficient code but the startup has
高效的代码，但创业公司有
always been a little bit of a an
总是有点
obsession of mine so part of that talk I
迷恋我的，所以我在那段话中
gave last year was sort of the beginning
去年给的有点开端
of some of the research that I've been
我曾经做过的一些研究
doing maybe the last year or so so this
大概在过去一年左右，所以这
is kind of a status update talk it's
是关于状态更新的话题
kind of here's where we are
有点像我们在这里
and I think you'll see we've done quite
我想你会看到我们已经做了很多
a lot of work actually in the last 12
在过去的12年中实际上有很多工作
months on this topic so you know the the
几个月的时间，所以您知道
the JVM is a complicated complicated
JVM是一个复杂的复杂
piece of machinery I don't understand it
机器我不明白
I mean I don't I didn't pretend to even
我的意思是我不假装没有
start trying to understand it but I have
开始尝试了解它，但是我有
tried to measure it okay so that was
试图衡量它好吧，那是
kind of where I am at the minute and
我一时的位置
that's where I am in my journey
那就是我在旅途中
maybe one day I'll actually be able to
也许有一天我真的可以
contribute something else but there's
贡献其他东西，但是有
sort of an impedance mismatch between
之间的阻抗不匹配
people who work on the JVM and people
在JVM上工作的人
who work on apps like as rain and spring
在雨和春天等应用上工作的人
developers we don't actually share the
我们实际上并不共享的开发者
same concerns what they do is awesome
他们所做的事情同样令人担忧
but they don't know how to build apps
但他们不知道如何构建应用
and what we do is equally awesome in a
我们所做的同样令人敬畏
different way so we don't understand how
不同的方式，所以我们不知道如何
the JVM works and somehow we've got to
JVM正常工作，我们必须
meet in the middle and so hopefully you
在中间相遇，所以希望你
know this will contribute with something
知道这会有所贡献
towards that effort if nothing else and
朝着那个努力前进
it's certainly been quite an important
这当然是非常重要的
piece of that has been a lot of
其中有很多
important work done not by me in the
重要的工作不是我在
spring team this year and I hope that
今年的春季队，我希望
some of it was influenced by me by what
其中一些受到我的影响
I've been doing here
我一直在这里
so I'd like to sort of take you through
所以我想带你通过
the journey a little bit show you what
旅程有点告诉你什么
I've been measuring I've been doing a
我一直在测量我一直在做
lot of work on JVM startup time but that
关于JVM启动时间的大量工作，但这
doesn't mean that there aren't other
并不意味着没有其他
performance and resource issues that we
我们遇到的性能和资源问题
can study there are other people
可以学习还有其他人
actually in the spring engineering team
实际上在春季工程团队
doing run more runtime benchmarks and
做更多的运行时基准测试
things like that those are also valuable
那些东西也很有价值
I just don't have time to talk about
我只是没有时间谈论
everything today so I'm going to talk
今天的一切，我要谈谈
about my startup time work so I'm going
关于我的启动时间工作，所以我要去
to talk because that's you know it's a
说话，因为那是你知道这是一个
pain point right every who's got an
痛点对每个有
integration test suite that's a little
集成测试套件，有点
bit slow yeah so it would be good to
有点慢，所以这对
know why at least wouldn't it even if we
知道为什么至少不会，即使我们
can't improve it but it turns out we can
不能改善它，但事实证明我们可以
improve it so stay tuned so I'm going to
改善它，所以请继续关注，以便
talk about you know what if you thought
谈论你知道如果你想
that a nasty integration test suite that
一个讨厌的集成测试套件
you wish was running faster what is it
您希望运行速度更快是什么
that's happening why why is it slow what
这就是为什么为什么它慢了什么
is it that can you can you actually
可以吗？
blame spring for any of that well you
怪罪于春天
can blame it some of some of it I'm sure
我可以责怪其中的一些
you can but not as much as you might
你可以，但不能尽你所能
sometimes think you know when you're
有时以为你知道你什么时候
tearing your hair out and you want to
扯头发，你想
throw your computer out the window it's
把电脑丢到窗外
probably not spring that is
可能不是春天
fundamentally responsible for the
从根本上负责
problem that you're experiencing and I
我遇到的问题
think now that I can you know stand here
现在想想我能知道你站在这里吗
and claim that we've measured it and
并声称我们已经对其进行了测量
we've done the best that we can to
我们已经尽力做到了
improve every bit that we could so I'll
尽我们所能改善我
talk about some the tools that I used
谈谈我使用的一些工具
doing this measurement exercise I'll
我做这个测量练习
talk about various options that you've
谈谈您拥有的各种选择
got for improving your life if you have
如果有的话，可以改善生活
this slow startup
这个缓慢的启动
and some of them every time I give this
每次我给他们一些
talk I'm happy to say I have to trust
谈话我很高兴地说我必须信任
one off the list because every time I
不在名单上，因为每次
measure something identifiable there's
测量可以识别的东西
somebody clever in the spring framework
春季框架中有人聪明
or spring b-team fixes something and
或春季B队解决了一些问题，
then I don't have to talk about it
那我就不用说了
anymore
不再
but I'll mention a few of those as we go
但我会在其中提及一些
along because they're not all in
一直以来，因为他们并不全都在
production yet so they're they're new
生产，所以他们是新的
things they're probably worth knowing
他们可能值得知道的事情
about so I'll talk about how to speed up
关于，所以我将谈论如何加快
that time and start of time is very
那个时间和开始的时间非常
correlated with the integration test
与整合测试相关
suite and I'll talk about ongoing work
套件，我将谈论正在进行的工作
what we're still doing and what we might
我们仍在做什么以及我们可能会做什么
see in the future so just couple of
看到未来，所以只有几个
pictures to start off this is now quite
图片开始这是现在
an old one more than six months old as
一个超过六个月大的老
you think but it still tells a decent
你认为，但这仍然说明一个体面的
story so it's different sample apps
故事，所以它是不同的示例应用程序
they're all the same feature set they're
它们都是相同的功能集
all spring big nettie a single HTTP
整个春季的大nettie一个HTTP
endpoint so it's like a hello world but
端点，所以就像一个世界
with you know at full HTTP set and these
与您知道完整的HTTP集和这些
are start startup times from my lap
从我腿上开始启动的时间
measured on my laptop which isn't you
在我的笔记本电脑上测得不是
know particularly powerful or fast or
知道特别强大或快速或
anything so when I started these
所以当我开始这些
measurements we had an app that could
测量我们有一个可以
start in thirteen hundred milliseconds I
从一千三百毫秒开始
think that was with spring the 2.0 and
认为那是与春天2.0和
we tweaked things a bit and we got to
我们调整了一些东西，然后
springle 2.1 we were starting to see
Springle 2.1我们开始看到
improvements so that's like down from
改善，就像从
1300 to less than twelve hundred
1300至少于一千二百
milliseconds I could tell you the
毫秒，我可以告诉你
differences the difference I will become
差异，我将成为
clear actually when I show another
当我显示另一个时，实际上清除
picture so I'll talk more about that
图片，所以我将进一步讨论
later and then I started playing around
后来我开始玩
with a new feature at the time
当时有新功能
welcome springle to anyway and Spring
无论如何欢迎springle和春天
Framework five which is functional being
功能性框架五
definitions and I'll explain more about
定义，我将详细说明
that there's a spring tips video on it
上面有一个弹簧提示视频
if you want to learn a bit more from
如果您想从中学到更多
Josh and I was able to run the same app
Josh和我能够运行相同的应用程序
in basically half the time so that
在基本上一半的时间内
looked promising and I looked a bit
看起来很有希望，我看起来有点
looked into that a bit more there are
调查了更多
two versions of that one of them uses
其中一个使用的两个版本
spring beat that's bunk I'll refer to
我要提到的春风
bunk later and one of them doesn't use
稍后上铺，其中之一不使用
spring beat so if you take out at the
春拍，所以如果你在
time this this gap is now almost closed
现在这个差距现在几乎被消除了
off actually because the spring boot
断掉实际上是因为弹簧靴
overhead we looked into that and
开销，我们调查了
researched it a lot
研究了很多
there isn't a Sweden spring boot not
没有瑞典的弹簧靴
spring boot there is about a 15
春季靴子大约有15
milliseconds or something it's not not
毫秒或并非如此
really that much but the reason that I
真的那么多，但是我的原因
like to show the site is this one so
喜欢显示该网站是这样的
this is startup time for the same
这是相同的启动时间
application when the class loader is
类加载器是
already warm the JVM is already warm so
JVM已经预热了，所以
I've started the app and I've closed the
我已经启动了应用程序，并关闭了
application context and then started it
应用程序上下文，然后启动它
again close run close run close run like
再次关闭运行，关闭运行，关闭运行，像
that and then it's not it's dramatic
那不是戏剧性的
right then if this is properly a factor
好的，如果这是一个适当的因素
of 10 faster so that tells me something
10的速度更快，这告诉了我一些东西
I mean that tells me something about
我的意思是告诉我一些有关
this the fundamental nature of the way
这是方法的基本性质
that the JVM currently as it's designed
目前设计的JVM
they all work like this class loading
它们都像此类加载一样工作
like that's like 80 90 percent at the
像是80 90％
time on startup is class loading and if
启动时间是类加载，如果
you take one message away from this talk
你从这个谈话中走了一条信息
that's it class loading what do you get
这就是类加载您得到什么
for when you load a class you get a
因为当您加载课程时，您会得到一个
feature so if your app has features you
功能，如果您的应用具有功能
have to load classes it takes a little
必须加载类需要一点时间
bit longer when it's cold okay when it's
有点冷的时候还可以
warm it doesn't
温暖不
so there's anybody ever used dev tools
所以有人用过开发工具
spring through dev tools enough people
通过足够的开发人员工具
to know what it means I'll show you I'll
知道我要告诉你的意思
show you what it means well that's
告诉你这意味着什么
basically what we
基本上我们
here dev tools is a warm JVM just
这里的开发工具只是一个温暖的JVM
restarting in application context we
在应用程序上下文中重启
throw away the class later build a new
扔掉班级，以后再建一个新的
one that's actually the same exactly the
实际上完全一样的一个
same experiment I did there so some
我在那里做过同样的实验
interesting observations this graph sort
这个图有趣的观察
of means slightly off the topic of
的意思稍微偏离主题
startup time but it's still there so
启动时间，但仍然存在
this is actually showing you why spring
这实际上告诉你为什么春天
be two point one and two point two are
是两点一和两点二是
so much better so on the y-axis I've got
好得多，所以在y轴上
a startup time it's the same app that
启动时间是相同的应用程序
blue is the blue from the pre the first
蓝色是从先到先的蓝色
slide so that's the thirteen hundred
滑动到一千三百
milliseconds and then what I do is I
毫秒然后我要做的是
squeeze the max heap size minus X M X
压缩最大堆大小减去XMX
right 100 Meg's 50 Meg's 10 Meg's and I
对100兆欧的50兆欧的10兆欧和我
squeeze it until the point where you get
挤压直到你得到
this hockey stick and that's basically
这个曲棍球棒，基本上
beyond that the app can start and
除此之外，该应用程序可以启动并
garbage collection wins and you get an
垃圾收集赢了，你得到了
out of memory error on startup it's
启动时出现内存不足错误
quite especially with older versions of
尤其是对于旧版本的
spring dude it's quite a characteristic
春天花花公子，这是一个很有特色
and quite a steep curve and ok they so
而且曲线很陡，好吧，所以
then the red one is spring break two
那么红色是春假二
point one so that's where we were in
点一，那就是我们所在的地方
sort of October last year that's amazing
去年十月真是太神奇了
I that's a really big difference so we
我的确有很大的不同，所以我们
went down from
从下降
an app with Nettie in like 25 megabytes
带有Nettie的应用（大约25兆字节）
of heap down to ten or even less and now
堆减少到十个甚至更少，现在
in spring boot 2.2 they pushed it
在春季靴子2.2中，他们推了它
illegally even a little bit of further
非法甚至进一步
so you can happily run it in ten legs
所以你可以愉快地用十个腿跑
you can go down to eight six maybe even
你甚至可以下降到八六点
you know six six megabytes of heat you
你知道六六兆字节的热量
can still run it it's not going to be
仍然可以运行它不会
happy but you can still run it and the
很高兴，但是您仍然可以运行它，并且
lines are the bottom there is our bunk
线是底部，这是我们的铺位
so the boot application with functional
因此启动应用程序具有功能
beam definitions and that's even more
光束定义，甚至更多
impressive right so I can drive that
令人印象深刻的权利，所以我可以开车
right down it doesn't really have that
下来真的没有那个
hockey stick even there's a there's a
曲棍球棒甚至有一个
it's - I can't detect it because I can't
是-我无法检测到它，因为我无法
see the difference between running and
看看跑步和跑步之间的区别
not running there's no gradual change
没有运行就没有逐渐的变化
between the two suddenly it just stops
在两者之间突然停止
running so that's with two point one
运行，所以有两点一
spring be two point one spring B to
弹簧是两点一弹簧B到
Point C and the reason this is
点C及其原因
informative is because well the class
信息丰富是因为好班
loading that I just explained has to
我刚才解释的加载必须
still happen no you're never going to
仍然发生不，你永远不会
get away from man if you book whole JVM
如果您预定了整个JVM，请远离人
you need to start the classes start the
您需要开始上课
application needs loaders classes there
应用程序在那里需要加载程序类
are things we can do in the framework
是我们可以在框架中做的事情
optimizations we can make to stop
我们可以停止的优化
garbage collection from needing to
垃圾收集从需要到
happen as much and that has actually
发生了很多，实际上
been acquired of dramatic improvement in
获得了巨大的进步
Springville 2.1 and 2.2 and that's a
Springville 2.1和2.2，那就是
different way of telling that story so I
用不同的方式讲那个故事，所以我
haven't got a 2.2 picture but it's
没有2.2图片，但是
basically the same as 2.1 this is these
与2.1基本相同，这是这些
are flame graphs generated by a tool
是由工具生成的火焰图
called
叫
a sink profiler which is really neat if
水槽轮廓仪，如果
any anybody used a sink profiler before
任何人之前都使用过水槽轮廓仪
it's great you can attach it to a
很好，您可以将其附加到
running Java process and it hardly
运行Java进程，几乎没有
affects the runtime performance but you
影响运行时性能，但您
get nice pretty flame graphs out of it
从中获得漂亮的漂亮火焰图
like for free so he wouldn't and they're
喜欢免费，所以他不会，他们是
nice you can click on them and zoom in
不错，您可以单击它们并放大
and you can do searches on the
您可以在
text in them anyway so each flame is a
无论如何在其中输入文字，以便每个火焰都是
method call essentially and the stack
本质上方法调用和堆栈
above it is nested method calls for this
上面是为此的嵌套方法调用
method calls that one pulls out and
方法调用一个退出，
pulls that one pulls that one and the
拉那个拉那个那个
width of the flame is is the number of
火焰的宽度是多少
samples in the profiler so it's roughly
在探查器中采样，因此大致
proportional to the time spent doing
与花费的时间成正比
this doing whatever he was doing and
无论他在做什么，
these are at startup so it is just the
这些都是在启动时，所以
first like you know second of an
首先像你知道的第二
applications life and the important
应用程序的生命和重要
thing is they're actually very similar
事实是它们实际上非常相似
looking apart from this angry little red
除了这个愤怒的小红色
and yellow blob over here and what that
和黄色的斑点在这里，那是什么
is is red and yellow means it doesn't
是红色和黄色表示不是
mean angry actually it means not in user
表示生气，实际上意味着不在用户中
memory so this is the garb this is the
记忆，所以这是服装，这是
JVM doing garbage collection and you can
JVM进行垃圾收集，您可以
see in the spring be two point one two
看到春天是两点一二
pointy we just squeeze that then what
尖尖的，我们只是挤压那
you squeeze that the further to the
你挤压到更远
right that hockey stick goes that's what
曲棍球棒走了就是这样
we did I know a lot of that is it's
我们知道很多吗？
through avoiding usage of api's that are
通过避免使用api
in the jdk in fact so the jdk has a lot
实际上在dDK中，因此dk有很多
of useful stuff in it right but they
里面有用的东西，但是他们
also have to be very cautious sometimes
有时也必须非常谨慎
when they have to make you know you make
当他们必须让你知道你做的时候
a method call to let's say class stuff
让我们说类东西的方法调用
get declared methods that one lists all
获取声明的方法，其中列出了所有方法
of the clap the methods in a class makes
类中方法的拍手声
a copy of it for you and that's where
为您准备的副本，在那里
the garbage comes from so there's a
垃圾来自所以有一个
coffee every time you call class don't
每次上课时不要喝咖啡
get the cloud methods you get an extra
获得云方法，您可以获得额外收益
copy and garbage builds up so if you can
复制并堆积垃圾，如果可以的话
avoid doing that which we found several
避免这样做，我们发现了几个
ways to do in the spring big 2.1 2.2 if
春季大的方法2.1 2.2如果
you can avoid doing that you can avoid
你可以避免这样做，你可以避免
the garbage collection here so that's
这里的垃圾收集是
what that's what's happening there
那是怎么回事
so often the best way to see this is
所以通常最好的方式是
with a nice demo so what I'll do is I
一个很好的演示，所以我要做的是
could do hello world like the apps that
可以像
I was just showing but I thought it
我只是展示而已
would be nice to show a sort of real
会很高兴展示出一种真实的
application now this is the pet clinic
现在申请这是宠物诊所
you've seen the pet Finnick everyone's
您已经看到了宠物Finnick每个人的
seen their pet clearing so it's sort of
看到他们的宠物清理，这有点
a real application is a spring boots
一个真正的应用是弹簧靴
shade spring day they're JPA app it has
他们是JPA应用程式，
like three entities or something like
像三个实体或类似的东西
that and it has thyme leaf as a UI in a
并以百里香叶作为UI
database and this is okay so this is pet
数据库，这还可以，所以这是宠物
clinic from master spring project master
春季项目负责人的诊所
I'm going to actually make it worse by
我实际上会使情况变得更糟
downgrading spring boot to 2.0 just so
将Spring Boot降级到2.0
you can see how dramatic the change is
您可以看到变化是多么巨大
so this may may even rebuild that so
所以这甚至可能会重建
it's happy and then I'm gonna go into my
很高兴，然后我要进入我的
pet clinic application here's the
宠物诊所的应用程序是
application just standard spring deep
应用只是标准弹簧深
stuff very small amount of code run as
很少的代码作为
java application
Java应用程序
and I've already got launches set up for
而且我已经为
this in the IDE so it's giving me a
这在IDE中，所以给了我一个
choice
选择
so this is my crappy laptop this is my
这是我笨拙的笔记本电脑，这是我的
experience launching spring the pet
体验发射宠物的春天
clinic 98.7 seconds I was gonna say 98.7
诊所98.7秒我要说98.7
feels about right yeah I mean people
感觉不错，是的，我是说人
were used to that kind of crap but let's
习惯了这种废话，但让我们
see what happens okay so I'm going to do
看看会发生什么，所以我要去做
couple of things I'm going to change
我要改变的几件事
this to 2.2 whoops
这个到2.2
you only live once don't you say I might
你只活过一次你不说我可以
as well do snapshot
快照也一样
bill - snapshot that look right just see
帐单-看起来正确的快照
the same little maven dancers before I'm
我之前一样的小舞者
also going to so as I go through the
当我经历
presentation I'll explain some of the
演讲中，我将解释一些
things I'm doing now I'm going to
我现在正在做的事情
exclude a couple of things from the
从中排除几件事
classpath so pet clinic doesn't use JSON
classpath，因此宠物诊所不使用JSON
there's no reason they need for it -
他们没有理由需要它-
there at all and I'm going to change the
在那里，我将改变
logging implementation from the default
从默认日志记录实现
so the logging is by default in the
因此默认情况下，
spring boots log back and I'm going to
春季靴子登录回来，我要去
just switch that around so I'm going to
只是切换一下，所以我要
exclude those two things and then I'm
排除这两件事，然后我
gonna go into the dependencies so
会进入依赖关系
everybody following what I'm doing here
每个人都跟着我在这里做什么
I'm going to insert SL f4j the JDK just
我要插入SL f4j JDK
the fastest lobular is it isn't the
最快的小叶不是
nicest it is it's a horrible logo jdk
最好的是，这是一个糟糕的徽标jdk
logging but it's faster so not much but
日志记录，但速度更快，但不多
you know a bit so it don't make a
你知道一点所以它不会
difference and then I'm just gonna run
差异，然后我就跑
this app again okay so now we're ready
这个应用程序又可以了，所以现在我们准备好了
we're going to get it run as java
我们将使其以Java运行
application this time I'm going to
这次我要去申请
please choose the one called flags
请选择一个称为标志
because I put some command line flags on
因为我在上面放了一些命令行标志
the JVM and I'll show you what those are
JVM，我会告诉你这些是什么
in a minute ready healthy nose okay less
一分钟内准备好健康的鼻子
than 30 seconds I reckon if I did it a
我认为如果超过30秒
few times you probably see two point
几次你可能会看到两点
seven two point eight that's all right
七个二点八就可以了
it's man
是男人
I would say that wasn't me that did that
我会说那不是我做的
right I mean I thought I did was just
对，我是说我以为我只是
mentioned to people a few times that
有人提到过几次
because you could make it faster you
因为你可以使其更快
could make it faster and they did it
可以使其更快，他们做到了
yeah so the flag will come up on the
是的，所以旗帜会升到
slides in a minute so what did I do and
在一分钟内滑动，所以我该怎么做，
how much of those which of those things
那些东西中有多少
have the biggest impact well spring
对春天影响最大
Spring Break two points you have a big
春假两点你有很大
impact where there are some features in
影响其中的某些功能
the spring boot to point to as well that
弹簧靴也要指出
I switched on there so we can have a
我打开那里，所以我们可以有一个
look at so how did I make it go faster
看，所以我怎么让它更快
I did some class path exclusions I'll
我做了一些课堂路径排除
talk about the details later I didn't
以后再说说细节
use the spring conduct context indexer
使用春季行为上下文索引器
does anybody ever try that
有没有人尝试过
I was talking to bed round today and he
我今天在床上睡觉，他
did so and I know some people use it
这样做，我知道有人使用它
it's an application
这是一个应用程序
it's an annotation processor it's been
这是一个注释处理器
in spring since I think four point
在春天，因为我认为四点
something spring for thing to you maybe
春天对你有好处
you just put it on the classpath an air
你只是把它放在课堂上
generates an index of the components you
生成您的组件的索引
know when you do a component scan and it
知道何时进行组件扫描及其
looks in all the packages in your
在您的所有包裹中查找
application for a component annotations
组件注释的应用
it just makes an index of that so it
它只是做一个索引，所以它
doesn't have to do it again no it turns
不必再做一次
out that the spring was never doing very
春季从来没有做得很好
much work there people you should say
你应该说很多工作
component scanning expensive component
组件扫描昂贵的组件
something's expensive so we call this in
东西很贵，所以我们称之为
there and prove to them it wasn't but
在那里向他们证明不是
it's a little bit faster the more beans
豆越多，速度就快一点
you've got so the more impact you get
你有更多的影响力
with pet clinic I don't know there might
在宠物诊所，我不知道有没有
be a dozen beans tops components can
一打豆顶组件就可以
beings and you might you could measure
存在，你也许可以衡量
the difference like it would be you know
那样的区别就是你知道
10 milliseconds or something you want
10毫秒或您想要的东西
the 10 milliseconds usually or if you've
通常是10毫秒，或者
got an app with 10,000 beans definitely
肯定有一个包含10,000个bean的应用程序
worth it
值得
I used to say and it broke my heart to
我曾经说过，这让我很伤心
say that don't use the actuators if you
说如果您不使用执行器
can afford nuts
买得起坚果
because it was if you start using
因为那是如果您开始使用
actuators in spring boo 2.0 it's gonna
Spring boo 2.0中的执行器
be you know more than half a second
你知道超过半秒吗
maybe even a second you know seven eight
也许一秒钟你就知道七点八分
hundred milliseconds so if you can
一百毫秒，如果可以的话
afford not to you then you know you get
负担不起你，那么你知道你得到
that back however when you know we
那回不过当你知道我们
looked at that in more detail the spring
春天更详细地看了一下
boot team decided to make some changes
引导团队决定进行一些更改
and since actually since spring we 2.0
自从春天以来我们2.0
most of the web endpoints were not
大多数网络端点不是
enabled by default anyway there's no
无论如何默认情况下都没有启用
point actually creating all of those
实际上创建所有这些点
beans so they just switch them off and
豆，所以他们只是关闭它们，
unless their enables and then every that
除非他们启用，然后每
problem went away so I didn't do that
问题消失了，所以我没有那样做
with disparate effects on it just now if
只是对它有不同的影响
I had I might have squeezed another near
我本来可能会挤在另一个附近
a couple of maybe twenty milliseconds or
大概二十毫秒或
something but it's much better than it
东西，但比它好得多
was in spring new 2.2 so use spring
是在春季新2.2，所以使用春季
break to Point C and it's not GAA GAA I
突破C点，不是GAA GAA I
know so if you can't do that use two
知道所以如果你不能做到这一点，请使用两个
point one it's still better this one I
我说的第一点还是更好
think they also put a lot of effort into
认为他们也付出了很多努力
improving so it still helps but not much
改善，因此仍然有帮助，但作用不大
okay so you might get another you know
好吧，所以你可能会得到另一个你知道的
few tens of milliseconds out of this
几十毫秒
spring dot config dot location is where
弹簧点配置点位置在哪里
your application dot properties file is
您的应用程序点属性文件是
and if you know where it is you can tell
如果你知道它在哪里，你可以告诉
spring boot where forget where to go and
春季靴子哪里去哪里忘了
look and it doesn't have to go searching
看，它不必去搜索
for it because it will it'll search for
为此，因为它将搜索
you know um application type properties
你知道应用程序类型的属性
application yam a little look in the
应用山药在
classifier that look in a file system
在文件系统中查找的分类器
it'll look in subdirectories will so if
它会在子目录中查找
you can stop it from doing that it saves
您可以阻止它执行以节省费用
a little bit of time I also used to say
我也常说一点时间
switch off jmx if you're not using it
如果您不使用它，请关闭它
because it's enabled by default and it
因为它是默认启用的
does cost something right the MX being
确实花费了一些正确的MX
the MB manager thing takes some time to
MB管理器需要花费一些时间
start up in the JDK they made that the
在JDK中启动，他们使
default in the spring B to Point C so
在弹簧B中默认为C点
you have to enable it by default now so
您现在必须默认启用它，因此
I don't I no longer have to advise that
我不再需要建议
but if he now if you're looking for
但是如果他现在正在寻找
weathers JMX end points are then you
天气JMX终点就是你
need to switch them on back on again
需要重新打开它们
another thing that happened in Spring
春天发生的另一件事
Break 3.2 was lazy beam definition so
Break 3.2是懒惰的光束定义，所以
this has been a feature of spring spring
这一直是春天的特征
the frame works since I think maybe
该框架有效，因为我认为
spring - it's anybody know if it's
春天-有人知道
before that lazy lien definitions so in
在那个懒惰的留置权定义之前
the XML you used to have a flag lazy
您曾经懒惰的XML
equals true on the XML and it wasn't
在XML上等于true，但不是
really used very much but there wasn't
真的用了很多，但是没有
much point because especially in the old
很多点，因为尤其是在旧的
days when you had that XML file you know
您拥有该XML文件的日子
X depends on Y and Y depends on said
X取决于Y，Y取决于
everything depends on something so even
一切都取决于某件事，即使
if they're all lazy as soon as you
如果他们一早就懒惰
create one of them the whole object
创建整个对象之一
graph has to be created so there wasn't
图必须创建，所以没有
much point but one thing I noticed doing
有很多要点，但我注意到一件事
this work was that with spring beat also
这项工作是因为春季跳动
configuration it's all-you-can-eat right
配置，任您选择
it's like you put something on the
就像你在上面放了一些东西
classpath you're gonna get a beat
你会被击败的classpath
because you know rest templates on the
因为您知道其他模板
class faster you're gonna get a rest
上课更快，你会休息
template actually it's not a rest
模板实际上不是休息
templates to rest template builder but
模板休息模板生成器，但是
you know what I mean and if you didn't
你知道我的意思，如果你不知道
use it
用它
that was a waste right when nobody had
当没有人拥有时，那是一种浪费
to load that class class loading is
加载该类的类加载是
expensive nobody had to create that you
昂贵的人无须创造你
know instance so we looked at that and
知道实例，所以我们看着那个
we decided that it was an interesting
我们认为这很有趣
thing to do just to set all beam
要做的只是设置所有光束
definitions to lazy and see what
懒惰的定义，看看什么
happened and what happened was I think
发生了什么事，我想
in the pet clinic that was probably
在宠物诊所里
probably a good second maybe a bit more
大概一秒钟好一点
than one point one point something
比一点一点一点
seconds you know more than a thousand
你知道一千多秒
milliseconds from lazy beam definitions
延迟光束定义的毫秒数
just stuff that you know may eventually
你可能最终会知道的东西
be used let's say you know the health
假设您知道健康
endpoint the health endpoint is there if
如果存在端点，则运行状况端点存在
you ever need it you'll be able to ping
您将需要ping通
it and it will then get created lazily
它，然后它将被懒惰地创建
now the spring group team very sensibly
现在春季组队非常明智
there
那里
I think Andy wrote a blog about this he
我认为Andy为此写了一个博客，
pointed out when they announced this
指出他们宣布这一点时
feature it might not be something you
功能可能不是你
want to do in production because in
想要生产，因为
production
生产
you'd rather fail on startup if there's
如果出现以下情况，您宁愿启动失败
going to be a problem right you'd might
可能会成为一个问题
I'd rather do that anyway so so we left
我还是愿意这样做，所以我们离开了
the default as not lazy but at
默认为不偷懒，但在
development time right when you're
适时的开发时间
making a change testing and make change
进行变更测试并进行变更
this that make change that's it what all
这就是改变的全部
you want then is just as fast as
然后，您想要的速度与
possible and when you're writing those
可能，当你写那些
integration tests if you're only using a
集成测试（如果您仅使用
small number of you know small slice of
你知道的一小部分
the application why do you need to
该应用程序为什么需要
bother loading all that the other beans
麻烦加载其他所有豆子
and that so that's definitely a good
那绝对是一个很好的选择
thing to do in the development time
开发时间要做的事情
another thing that has been improved but
另一件事已经改善，但
not to the extent that I can cross this
不至于我可以跨越这个范围
off the fat jar sprinkly fat jazz like
脱掉胖子罐子，撒上胖子爵士乐
brilliance right there an excellent way
辉煌就在那里
to take binary code that's executable
采取可执行的二进制代码
anywhere and just give it to somebody
随便把它给别人
and say here's jar file run it but if
并说这是jar文件运行它，但是如果
you do Jabbar - jar it's a bit slower
你做贾巴尔-罐子它有点慢
than if you unpack it and then do Java -
比您解压缩然后再使用Java的情况-
CP created the classpath I mean you know
CP创建了类路径，我的意思是你知道
specify the main domain class it's a bit
指定主域类
slower because of the indirection I need
由于我需要间接
the Java - John has to go into the jar
Java-约翰必须进入罐子
to find the jars and so there's just you
找到罐子，所以只有你
know the jar loading thing is a little
知道罐子里的东西有点
bit inefficient one there's one change
效率低下，只有一种改变
that they made a spring big two point
他们提出了春季大两点
two which improves this which is which
两个改善了这是哪个
will affect you if you're using for
如果您用于
instance Cloud Foundry because on how
实例Cloud Foundry，因为如何
foundry what they have they have
铸造他们所拥有的
unpacked the jar for you already
已经为您打开了包装
but they weren't you they aren't using
但他们不是你，他们没有使用
the main method from your cart from your
您购物车中的主要方法
application they're using the spring
他们正在使用弹簧的应用程序
boot ja launcher so that in that
启动ja启动器，这样
scenario we now don't have we don't go
现在我们没有的情况下我们不去
jar jar we go straight to the file
罐子罐子，我们直接去文件
system so that was an improvement
系统，这是一个改进
actually in Spring Break - point two so
实际上在春假期间-所以第二点
it's the unpacked jar is always faster
这是打开包装的罐子总是更快
it's
它的
a little bit faster still if you use the
如果您使用
applications own main class not the
应用拥有自己的主类而不是
spring Boop on okay here's one where I
Spring Boop好的，这是我的地方
get dinged all the time if there are any
如果有的话会一直流连忘返
JVM experts in the audience they always
他们始终是观众中的JVM专家
come up to me afterwards and say don't
之后来找我说不要
do that
去做
but I still do it right because well you
但我还是做对了，因为你好
know you saw what happened to the tech
知道你看到技术发生了什么
clinic right so if you run the JVM with
诊所吧，所以如果您使用
some extra flags - no verify is a really
一些额外的标志-没有验证是真的
good one that will take that's not just
好人不仅会接受
a you know a few microseconds that's
你知道几微秒
like 30% of any app it will be 30% 40%
就像任何应用程式的30％一样，将会是30％40％
faster if you just - no verify what does
如果您只是，则可以更快-无需验证
it mean it means that the JVM is allowed
这意味着它允许JVM
to just load the class data and read the
只是加载类数据并读取
bytes read the byte code without
字节读取字节码不带
checking that it's valid byte code so
检查它是有效的字节码，以便
you know maybe you don't want to do it
你知道也许你不想做
in production that's fine it's your
在生产中很好是你的
choice but you know I'm gonna do that on
选择，但你知道我要去做
my IDE on my laptop I just downloaded
我刚刚下载的笔记本电脑上的IDE
the Java file I know it came from I know
我知道的Java文件来自我知道
the bytes are good you don't need to
字节很好，您不需要
tell me that the bytes are good just do
告诉我字节很好
it quickly all right so that's one that
很快就可以了，那就是那个
you could you could condition you could
你可以条件你可以
you know if you're running in a
你知道你是否正在跑步
container and you built the jar if you
容器，如果你建立了罐子
built the container you know what's in
建立了你知道里面有什么容器
it you can verify everything sort of
它可以验证一切
ahead of time that's I don't think
提前那是我不认为的
that's such a bad choice frankly but the
坦白说，这是一个糟糕的选择，但是
worst thing that happens really is that
确实发生的最糟糕的事情是
you know if you have it bad some bad
你知道你有没有不好
bytecode like an agent produces some bad
像代理这样的字节码会产生一些问题
bytecode that it wasn't in your control
不在您控制范围内的字节码
the JVM will crash you know it'll just
JVM将崩溃，您知道它只会
the process will just disappear and
该过程将消失，
you'll get no information about why it
您将无法获得任何信息
happened so if you're prepared to face
发生了，所以如果你准备面对
that kind of outcome then you can do it
这样的结果，那么你可以做到
play that game the other one is to do
玩另一场比赛
with the compiler the JIT compiler so in
与编译器的JIT编译器，所以在
the JVM when it's running it optimizes
JVM在运行时会进行优化
heavily optimized
高度优化
take the bytecode turns it into machine
将字节码变成机器
code and you can control how much work
代码，您可以控制多少工作
it does with that with various
它与各种
command-line options this one says I
这个说我的命令行选项
don't know the details bit stop at some
不知道细节停在一些
level right don't go to full hog and
正确的水平不要全力以赴
that has a big effect on setup that
对设置有很大影响
means that it doesn't have to do a lot
意味着它不需要做很多事情
of analysis of the code paths that it's
的代码路径分析
running on startup it's about another
在启动时运行，这与另一个
percentage thing it's about another 10%
百分比的事情大约是另外10％
so those two things together between 30
所以这两件事之间30
and 50% improvement for pretty much any
50％的改善几乎可以
app so I could have done that with
应用程序，所以我可以做到这一点
spring do 2.0 and you would have seen a
春天做2.0，你会看到一个
big improvement actually that would have
实际上会有很大的改善
gone down from 9 seconds down to you
从9秒下降到你
know five and a half or something but
知道五年半左右，但
the other two and a half seconds there
还有另外两个半秒
was all that other stuff all right that
其他所有的东西都可以吗
was all that other stuff and at the
是所有其他东西，在
bottom of this slide is stuff that I
这张幻灯片的底部是我
didn't do yet so auto-configuration I'll
还没有做，所以我会自动配置
come I'll come back to that is all you
来吧，我会回到那就是你
can eat right at enable auto
可以在enable auto吃饭
configuration is a nice spring boot
配置是一个不错的弹簧靴
application I like using it it's you
我喜欢使用的应用程序是你
know takes takes the bird in a way I
知道花鸟以一种方式
don't have to think about what's
不必去想什么
happening but yeah for some people they
发生了，但是对某些人来说
don't like that and it does mean that he
不喜欢那样，这确实意味着他
might be including stuff features that
可能包括一些东西功能
you're not using so if you're if you can
您没有使用，如果可以的话
individually pick the auto
单独选择自动
configurations you might have slightly
您可能会有的配置
better side of performance it depends on
性能取决于更好的一面
your app it depends on you know which
您的应用取决于您知道哪个
ones he was using and whether they were
他正在使用的那些，以及是否
needed at startup and that sort of thing
启动时需要的东西
functional being definitions are also
功能存在定义也
very interesting I showed you that the
非常有趣，我告诉你
red blob was significantly faster than
红色斑点明显快于
the Blue Boar be the first but first
蓝野猪是第一但第一
first slide the pictures not as clear as
首先滑动图片不清晰
I any more so I do like functional being
我不再，所以我喜欢功能性的存在
definitions I'll show you more about
定义，我将向您详细介绍
them later but they're not necessarily
他们以后，但不一定
the only way to improve startup
改善创业的唯一途径
performance and they they are a
性能，他们是一个
significant significant sort of
重大的
program a bird and actually converting
编写一只鸟并进行实际转换
all the feel configuration to functional
所有的感觉配置到功能
is not cheap or easy and also in invert
不便宜也不容易，而且反过来
in brackets I put build a native image
在方括号中，我将构建本机图像
you've probably heard about growl VM
您可能听说过咆哮的虚拟机
they just had a ga release 19.0 right
他们刚刚发布了ga版本19.0
Ralphie and has this new feature where
Ralphie并具有此新功能，其中
you can take a Java program and compile
您可以使用Java程序进行编译
it to a binary image like you do with go
像使用go一样将其转换为二进制图像
lying or rust or something and the
说谎或生锈或其他东西
images that you create are small they
您创建的图像很小
run in quite small memory compared to
相比于
big JVM and they start up quickly so
大型JVM，它们很快启动，因此
that could be interesting right and
那可能很有趣，
Juergen mentioned it this morning
于尔根今天早上提到了它
already we are definitely going to be
我们已经肯定会
doing that with spring applications
用spring应用程序做到这一点
probably with some restrictions but not
可能有一些限制，但没有
too onerous however there's two
太繁重但是有两个
work-in-progress way it's in in brackets
进行中的方式放在方括号中
I don't think anybody's really ready to
我认为没有人真的准备好
go into production with this year and
今年开始生产，
the native image feature actually isn't
本机图像功能实际上不是
GA yet either so they released squirrel
GA还是这样，所以他们释放了松鼠
VM and they took that native image
VM，他们拍摄了本机映像
feature out for the last minute so they
在最后一刻精选出来，所以他们
left it in Developer Preview they call
留在他们称之为“开发人员预览”中
it so it's it's not GAA ok so another
所以不是GAA，所以另一个
summary screen and then basically you
摘要屏幕，然后基本上是您
can all either leave or go to sleep I
可以离开还是去睡觉我
don't think it beers ready yet though so
别以为啤酒还没有准备好
stick around if you want to know more
如果您想了解更多，请坚持
about the details so spring spring was
关于细节，所以春天是春天
always actually pretty lightweight that
总是很轻巧
one of the things I did in the demo last
我上次在演示中所做的一件事
year here was I just kind of I stripped
那一年我只是被剥夺了
an application down from spring to take
从春季开始申请
away some features take away feed them
离开一些功能带走养活他们
or take away more take away more until
或带走更多带走更多，直到
it was just spring just spring starting
那只是春天，只是春天的开始
up with nothing
一无所有
I know nettie new business or a lot
我知道新业务还是很多
logic no anything and it's really fast
逻辑上没有任何东西，而且速度非常快
rate I mean like you can start a spring
率，我的意思是就像你可以开始一个春天
application context in you know under 10
您知道10岁以下的应用程序上下文
milliseconds it's nothing so spring is
毫秒没什么，所以春天是
pretty lightweight on its own it's what
本身就很轻巧
you do with spring that you know is why
你用春天做，你知道为什么
that's why you use it
这就是为什么你使用它
so that's why why you want to be that
所以这就是为什么你想成为那个
one to be here but we do care about
一个人在这里，但我们确实在乎
performance a lot right wait this isn't
性能很好吧，这不是
a new thing for me I've been you know
对我来说我是新事物
obsessing about this for years
多年来迷恋这个
we have made some really truly amazing
我们做出了一些真正令人惊奇的事情
progress in the last year but we've
去年取得了进展，但我们已经
always cared about it
一直在乎
there are many optional features so
有很多可选功能
features are classes that needed to be
功能是需要
loaded so if you don't use them they
已加载，因此如果您不使用它们
won't cost you anything
不会花你任何钱
exploded war expenditure I mentioned
我提到的战争开支爆炸
that already I tried really hard to find
我已经尽力寻找
a difference between tomcat Jesse and
tomcat Jesse和
undertow because I know people have
因为我知道人们有
opinions I think undertake just about
我认为观点差不多
has the has the prize but you can't tell
有奖，但是你不知道
much like its marginal especially with
非常像它的边缘，特别是
tomcat 9 so that the most recent
tomcat 9这样最新
versions of tom can't do less on startup
版本的tom在启动时不能做不到
than they used to so there's actually
比他们过去的习惯
very little difference between the
之间的差异很小
server containers Nettie is a bit faster
服务器容器Nettie快一点
on startup but you know you're talking
在启动时，但是你知道你在说话
about 50 milliseconds you're not talking
你不说话约50毫秒
about and that's a constant that's not
关于，这是一个常数，不是
something that's going to go up or down
会上升或下降的东西
depending on how many beans you've got
取决于你有多少豆子
so it's not really that much of a
所以实际上并没有那么多
difference but really this is it the
区别，但实际上这就是
more features more classes are loaded 90
更多功能，更多类加载90
percent 80 90 percent at the time of
百分之80 90
startup is taken with class clothing so
创业是穿上班服的，所以
that's where you're gonna see the
那就是你要去的地方
difference functional being definitions
差异功能存在定义
I should say are interesting I changed
我应该说很有趣，我改变了
hands but maybe I didn't they are
手，但也许我不是
interesting but they're not going to
有趣，但他们不会
solve your problem I did at one point
一次解决您的问题
think that they would be the next the
认为他们将是下一个
next step but I'm not so sure it's nice
下一步，但我不确定是否很好
that they're there it's good to have an
他们在那里，有一个
option we can measure it but I'm not
选项，我们可以测量它，但我不是
sure it's actually all that interesting
确保这真的很有趣
at the end of the day anyway I can start
无论如何，我可以在一天结束时开始
a spring food application with an HTTP
一个带有HTTP的春季食品应用程序
endpoint full stack JSON rendering
端点全栈JSON呈现
everything in less than a second we
不到一秒钟的一切
yeah and use less than ten megabytes of
是的，使用少于十兆字节的
heat that's really their punchline so
加热才是他们的重点
the tools that I've been using for
我一直在使用的工具
benchmarks jmh it's the only sensible
基准jmh，这是唯一明智的选择
thing to use for JDK benchmarks it's a
用于JDK基准测试的东西
micro benchmark framework but on top of
微型基准框架，但最重要的是
that there's a thing that mark Halu from
哈卢来自某处
the spring team rate which is j-unit
春季队率，即j单位
integration for jmh so instead of at
jmh的集成，所以不是在
tests on a test method you right at
根据您所选择的测试方法进行测试
benchmark and that's pretty cool right
基准，这很酷吧
so it takes your method from a test
所以它需要您的方法进行测试
class essentially and just turns it into
本质上讲，将其变成
a benchmark so I've been using that all
一个基准，所以我一直都在用
the measurements that I show for
我显示的尺寸
start-up time basically do that and then
启动时间基本上是这样，然后
inside the test method they start a new
在测试方法内，他们开始一个新的
JVM new process with a new class path
JVM具有新类路径的新过程
and you know I play around with the
你知道我在玩
class path I played different games with
我玩过不同游戏的课堂路径
the features in the application by using
通过使用应用程序中的功能
the spring beat or take configuration
跳动或采取配置
essentially for profiling I've used a
本质上来说，我使用了
bunch of things async profiler is great
一堆东​​西异步探查器很棒
you get those flame graphs it's a very
你得到那些火焰图，这是一个非常
neat little tool I'm told there's
有人告诉我整洁的小工具
another one which is very similar called
另一个非常相似的叫做
honest profiler I think it's cool but
诚实的剖析器，我认为这很酷，但是
this one works for me often when I've
当我已经
seen those Fame graphs I need more
看到那些名望图，我需要更多
detailed information about where the
有关何处的详细信息
garbage collection pressure is
垃圾收集压力是
originating and the only tool I found
是我发现的唯一工具
that does anything for that is JMC Java
可以做到的就是JMC Java
Mission Control flight controller has a
任务控制飞行控制器具有
UI which has a specific view in it where
在其中具有特定视图的UI
you can look at tlad thread local
你可以看看本地的tlad线程
allocation buffer and that's the thing
分配缓冲区就是这样
that shows up in those flame graphs it's
在那些火焰图中显示出来的是
kind of temporary objects that are being
一种暂时的物体
churned essentially I'm in the stack but
搅动本质上我在堆栈中，但是
they need to be a
他们需要成为一个
before the next the next round of
在下一轮之前
garbage collection so you can see that
垃圾收集，所以你可以看到
think that stuff happening basically in
认为事情基本上发生在
flight controller I created a little
我创建了一个飞行控制器
tool I don't know if anybody's actually
我不知道是否有人
used it but you will find a lot of this
使用它，但您会发现很多
research in github in various repos one
在github中进行各种研究
of them is called spring beat startup
他们中的一个叫做春季跳动启动
that's in my personal github space and
在我个人的github空间中，
in there one of the sub projects in
在那儿有一个子项目
there is actually an app so it's a
实际上有一个应用程序，所以它是一个
spring bleed app that you can use - it's
您可以使用的Spring bleed应用程序-
not a spring Roo that it's it and it's a
不是弹簧Roo，就是这样，这是一个
Java app that you can use to run another
您可以用来运行另一个的Java应用程序
jar file and you know run it repeatedly
jar文件，您知道它会反复运行
start it up and stop it styled up and
启动它，然后停止它的样式，
stop there so I can stop it should
停在那里，所以我可以停下来
basically to reproduce a benchmark
基本上是重现基准
figure so you can get the timer tank
图，以便您可以获取计时器槽
fixed to start up I have used
修复了我曾经用过的启动
extensively my thing called a spring big
我的东西叫做春天大
thin launcher I used that to compute
瘦启动器，我用它来计算
class paths fundamentally although it
从根本上来说是类路径
was written originally originally to be
最初写成是
a different approach for packaging jar
包装罐子的另一种方法
files so that they're thin but
文件，以便它们很薄，但
executable it also has this class path
可执行文件，它也具有此类路径
computation feature that I think I've
我认为我具有的计算功能
used to basically change the class path
用于基本上改变班级路径
and it enabled more features for
并且启用了更多功能
benchmarks and I've also used a spec J
基准，我也使用了规格J
over some numbers I can flash them up
超过一些数字，我可以将它们刷新
don't really have time to go into all of
真的没有时间去研究所有
the details here but a few things to
这里的细节，还有一些要
notice the demo sample that's the blue
注意蓝色的演示样本
one from the first slide so it was at
第一张幻灯片上的一个，所以它在
the time that I drew that graph from the
我从中绘制该图的时间
slide it was thirteen hundred
滑到一千三百
milliseconds this one is nine hundred
毫秒，这是九百
nine hundred and thirty five so that's
九百三十五
the that's the improvements in the
那就是
spring be two point zero heat memory 13
弹簧是两点零热量记忆13
megabytes total memory that's an
兆字节的总内存
estimate it's a bit hard to estimate but
估计有点困难，但是
total memory 76 megabytes and you know
总内存76兆字节，您知道
five thousand classes and that's the
五千课，那是
thing that basic
那基本的东西
generates all of that heat on startup
在启动时产生所有这些热量
900 milliseconds is really nearly all
几乎是900毫秒
the time it takes to load 5600 classes
加载5600学时所需的时间
so generally speaking as you change so
所以一般来说，随着你的改变
I've got one with JDBC and one with
我有一个使用JDBC，另一个有
actuators as you can increase the number
执行器，因为您可以增加数量
of features you increase the startup
增加启动功能
time you increase the number of classes
你增加课程数量
this sequence here says so this is the
这个序列在这里说，所以这是
demo sample and then I start stripping
演示样本，然后我开始剥离
features out as I gave you further down
当我给你进一步介绍时
here more and more features are removed
这里越来越多的功能被删除
from that application until I get to the
从那个应用程序直到我到达
point where it's completely functional
指出它完全起作用的地方
and at that point it's running in 700
那时它在700
milliseconds but there's quite a lot of
毫秒，但是有很多
overhead there in terms of you know
就你知道那里的开销
maintaining the the application code
维护应用程序代码
I'll show you what that means this is
我会告诉你这是什么意思
interesting so you've got quite a tight
有趣，所以你很紧张
correlation it's not exactly a straight
相关性不完全是直的
line it's more like maybe two straight
线更像是两个直线
lines quite a tight correlation between
线条之间的紧密联系
number of classes loaded and startup
加载和启动的类数
time and I did this by changing the
时间，我通过更改
class path basically so it's almost the
基本上是班级路径，所以几乎
same application but running over and
相同的应用程序，但是运行了
over and some of the ones at the bottom
结束，还有一些在底部
here are not the same application
这里不是同一应用程序
they're the ones where I start you know
他们是我开始的地方
removing stuff manually and creating
手动删除内容并创建
functional bean definite definitions and
功能Bean定义和
stuff like that but they're all on the
这样的东西，但他们都在
same curve it's a pretty tight
相同的曲线非常紧
correlation and anywhere I found that
相关性，我发现的任何地方
they were deviating I went and looked at
他们偏离了我去看了看
then I found problems and fixed them so
然后我发现了问题并解决了
you can do that with your apps right you
你可以用你的应用程序做到这一点
could plot it on that and you can see if
可以将其绘制在上面，您可以查看是否
it was down here you'd be winning if it
它在这里，如果你会赢
was up here you'd be thinking that you
在这里，你会以为你
could probably find a problem in the
可能会发现一个问题
address if this one's interesting that
解决这个有趣的问题
one is spring boot application with
一个是Spring Boot应用程序
hibernate JPA so hibernate is winning
休眠JPA，因此休眠是成功的
all right everybody thinks hibernate is
大家都认为冬眠是
slow it's not compared to the number of
慢，它不与数量相比
classes that you have to load over 8000
您必须加载超过8000个课程
is actually pretty good
其实还不错
so the hibernate team it turns out are
所以事实证明，休眠团队
very aware of these garbage collection
非常了解这些垃圾收集
problems and they've highly optimized it
问题，他们已经对其进行了高度优化
so they've done a really good job there
所以他们在那里做得很好
need to move a bit quicker Webb flux and
需要更快地移动韦伯通量和
Nettie it's a little bit faster like I
Nettie像我一样快一点
said that's the demo application again
说这又是演示应用程序
there's a usual canonical sample so
有一个通常的规范样本，所以
you're down under 800 milliseconds for
您的时间不到800毫秒
that J log is the same thing but I did
J日志是一回事，但我做到了
the classpath exclusions so JSON and log
类路径的排除，所以JSON和日志
back are removed basically and hibernate
背部基本被移除并冬眠
validator I've done it validator I
验证程序我已经完成了验证程序我
forgot about that yeah so um the pepsin
忘了是的，所以胃蛋白酶
it needed - a validator I couldn't take
它需要-我无法接受的验证器
that out if you're not using it take it
如果您不使用它，那就把它拿走
out because that is you know it's a
出来，因为那是你知道这是一个
pretty much constant 60 70 milliseconds
几乎恒定60 70毫秒
maybe not that much maybe 50 at the
也许没有那么多50
friends on your platform and everything
平台上的朋友以及其他一切
you prosper
你兴旺
so here the JVM tweaks I talked about
所以在这里我谈到了JVM的调整
nines no verify and kids stuff at level
九分球没有验证，孩子们的水平
one I'll quickly mention that one so you
我会很快提到的一个
see some blogs especially older ones
查看一些博客，尤其是较旧的博客
about dev random you don't need to do
关于开发随机，你不需要做
that anymore by and large but I'm
总的来说，但我是
putting it up there just to remind you
放在那只是提醒你
it used to be a problem with all the
这曾经是所有的问题
versions of Tomcat and it isn't anymore
版本的Tomcat，现在已经不存在了
you can share nine is really interesting
你可以分享九个真的很有趣
so there's a feature called class data
所以有一个叫做类数据的功能
sharing CDF that I believe was invented
分享我认为是发明的CDF
for app servers like WebSphere and we'd
对于像WebSphere这样的应用服务器，我们会
love WebLogic but I'm not sure that's
喜欢WebLogic，但我不确定
true anymore because somebody told me
不再是真的，因为有人告诉我
different story recently but anyway ICDs
最近有不同的故事，但无论如何，ICD
it tries to take some of that class
它试图参加一些这样的课程
floating overhead and cache it so that
浮动开销并缓存它，以便
sounds like a good thing right
听起来不错
turns out that it's been in the Oracle
原来它已经在Oracle中了
JDK for a long time I don't know maybe
JDK很久了，我可能不知道
since Java 7 humans which other six I'm
自从Java 7人类以来，我还有另外六个
not sure and it's now available by
不确定，现在可以通过
default in openjdk so you can get your
openjdk中的默认设置，因此您可以获得
job at eleven version and use CDF and if
在11个版本上工作并使用CDF，如果
you see performance benchmarks from Java
您会看到Java的性能基准
11 JDK people they always switch this on
11个JDK人员，他们总是将其打开
because it helps but it's a pain it's
因为它有帮助，但这是一个痛苦
really difficult to generate all of the
真的很难产生所有的
cache data that you need you've got to
缓存您需要的数据
go through this long sort of multi-step
经过漫长的多步骤
process to get to the front row
到达第一行的过程
run it open j9 is the IBM JVM that they
运行它打开j9是他们的IBM JVM
donated to eclipse and with that you
捐给日食，并与你
just have to play these three
只需玩这三个
command-line options just go faster and
命令行选项只会更快，
it does it's amazing it's about it's not
它确实很棒，因为它不是
a dramatic they said that red and the
戏剧性的他们说红色和
blue are JDK a standard JDK eight and
蓝色是JDK，标准是JDK八，
open j9 it's a bit faster it's about
打开j9，它的速度要快一些
it's a percentage things about ten so
大约是百分之十
maybe fifteen if you're lucky they might
如果幸运的话，大概十五岁
be worth having and then they exploded
值得拥有，然后他们爆炸了
fast mouth obviously classpath exclusion
快嘴明显的类路径排斥
was okay I've mentioned Jackson a lot
没关系，我经常提到杰克逊
back open a validator definitely
一定要打开验证器
actuators I'm not so foolish I'm so
执行器我不是那么愚蠢我是如此
bearish about anymore I think you can
看空了我想你可以
leave those in it's probably fine you
把那些留在里面可能很好
might find other things though so the
可能会发现其他东西，所以
things the thing to look out for is
要注意的事情是
static initializers things that happen
静态初始化程序发生的事情
when class is loaded right and so these
当类正确加载时，这些
things are all about horrendous static
事情都是关于可怕的静态的
initializers in them actually not the
他们中的初始化器实际上不是
actuators those are the three things
执行器是三件事
lazy being so there are two features in
懒惰的存在，所以有两个功能
recent versions with spring boot one is
春季靴子的最新版本是
spring data del JPA repositories
Spring Data JPA存储库
bootstrap node equals lazy that was
引导节点等于懒惰
actually in spring be two point one i
实际上在春天是两点一
did that in the pet clinic that would be
是在宠物诊所做的
for the pet clinic where as three
对于宠物诊所，其中三个
entities that would probably be half a
实体可能是一半
second maybe seven hundred milliseconds
秒也许是七百毫秒
something like that that's worth having
这样的东西值得拥有
if you have a large number of entities
如果您有大量实体
it goes up proportionately it's amazing
它按比例上升，这太神奇了
so i you know you can create crazy
所以我知道你可以制造疯狂
applications with four hundred entities
四百个实体的应用程序
and they take you know a minute to start
他们花了您一分钟时间来开始
on my laptop and then you put make the
在我的笔记本电脑上，然后您将
repositories lazy and it goes down to
存储库懒惰，它下降到
two seconds amazing right
两秒钟惊人的权利
sometimes sometimes people miss Densham
有时人们会怀念Densham
misinterpret this this is just an
曲解这只是一个
observation sometimes when I've looked
当我看着时观察
at people's real applications and they
在人们的实际应用中，他们
were slow I found that they were abusing
很慢，我发现他们在滥用
her post construct they were doing
他们正在做的她的帖子构造
expensive stuff and they knew they were
昂贵的东西，他们知道他们是
doing it they were you know reading
这样做，你知道吗
files and going to databases and
文件并转到数据库
blocking in that posted stress and that
阻止发布的压力和
will definitely slow you down
一定会让你慢下来
when you're starting and then the system
当您启动时，然后系统
now in spring be 2.2 Spring main lazy
现在春季2.2春季主要懒惰
initialization equals true I did that in
初始化等于true我在
the pet clinic as well that probably got
宠物诊所也可能
me another second I should think so it
我应该再想一秒钟
was worth having okay so now we're at
值得拥有，所以现在我们在
the bottom of the list of things you can
您可以做的事情清单的底部
do so one thing you can try I read a
这样做一件事，你可以尝试我读一本
blog about this you can try it too in
关于此的博客，您也可以在
stead of using at enable auto
而不是使用启用自动
configuration you can try this other
配置你可以试试这个
annotation at import Auto configuration
导入自动配置时添加注释
and then you have to list you have to
然后你必须列出你必须
know which ones to list that's the hard
知道列出哪些是很难的
thing right so this is a just a standard
没错，这只是一个标准
nettie HTTP app with error handling just
带有错误处理的nettie HTTP应用程序
sort of my demo apps basically there's
我的演示应用程序基本上
the minimum set of stuff you need to run
您需要运行的最少材料集
an exit web flex at pet clinic it would
宠物诊所的出口网伸缩
have another for more caching know a bit
还有另一个用于更多缓存的知识
bit more than that maybe caching
比缓存还多
hibernate JPA data source
休眠JPA数据源
yeah probably another half a dozen or so
是的，大概还有六点左右
so you've got to curate that yourself
所以你必须自己整理
which is kind of a pain and I'm trying
这是一种痛苦，我正在尝试
to both I and Sebastian dealers he was
我和塞巴斯蒂安的经销商
talking about code through this morning
在今天早上讨论代码
we're both trying to think of nice
我们都在努力思考美好
programming models for identifying that
用于识别的编程模型
making that easier to do so if anybody
如果有人的话，这样做更容易
wants to do manual configuration it
想手动配置
should I believe be possible and should
我相信应该并且应该
be nicer to do than this but this is
比这更好做，但这是
this works it used to be a really big
这个作品曾经很大
thing and this it turned out that the
事情，事实证明，
big difference between the blue and the
蓝色和蓝色之间的巨大差异
red in my original slide was mainly this
我原始幻灯片中的红色主要是这个
mainly just the fact that I'd narrowed
主要是我缩小了范围
the configurations and when the you then
配置以及您何时
had it also lazy initialization and a
是否也懒惰初始化和
bunch of other stuff they didn't spring
一堆他们没有冒出来的东西
to point to it wasn't such a big
指出它不是那么大
difference if you have one picture this
如果你有一张照片就不同
or the shows that so some pet pet clinic
或显示一些宠物诊所
benchmarks blue is spring be
基准是春天
auto-configuration
自动配置
all-you-can-eat one of them is just a
所有你可以吃一个只是
standard this is pet clinic by the way
顺便说一句，这是宠物诊所
this not not the hello world standard
这不是你好世界标准
pet clinic and with actuators so
宠物诊所，并带有执行器
actuators off actuators on with
执行器关闭
actuators off I could get down to less
执行器关闭我可以减少到更少
than one and a half seconds starting the
不到一秒半的时间开始
pet clinic and then I've got the yellow
宠物诊所，然后我得到了黄色
which is manual beam definitions but I
这是手动光束定义，但我
guess without lazy so it's that one
猜不偷懒，就是那个
point nine seconds or something and red
点九秒左右或红色
is functional so the functional beam
是功能性的，所以功能性光束
definitions got me a little bit in that
定义让我有点
but not very much on this side there's
但在这边不是很多
an almost no difference that if the same
几乎没有区别，如果相同
functional beam definitions and
功能光束定义和
non-functional there's nothing so
没有功能就没有了
there's really its academic really and
真的有它的学术
the auto configuration again is a little
自动配置又有点
bit faster because of the lazy beam
有点慢，因为光束很懒
definitions so functional being
具有功能性的定义
definitions is interesting definitely
定义肯定很有趣
interesting because it doesn't use
有趣，因为它不使用
reflection right so this is the standard
反射正确，所以这是标准
and configuration a theme we have spring
和配置我们有春天的主题
has to look at these beans look at these
不得不看这些豆子，看看这些
classes analyze all the methods look at
类分析所有方法看
the annotations look at the names of
注释会查看
everything all using reflection and the
一切都使用反射和
reflection is fast rate it's not
反射速度快，不是
necessarily a bad thing but if you want
一定是一件坏事，但是如果你想
to avoid reflection you can and we've
为了避免反射，您可以，我们已经
done that you know since spring five
从春季五开始就知道了
we've had this this model where you can
我们有这个模型，您可以
write an application context initializer
编写应用程序上下文初始化器
and you can call on the generic
您可以致电通用
application context you can call an API
您可以调用API的应用程序上下文
register being a registered bean
注册是注册bean
register bean and that's the same code
注册bean，这是相同的代码
basically as a previous slide so that's
基本上是上一张幻灯片，所以
the process and then you can see why
这个过程，然后你会明白为什么
it's its reflection free you can also
它是无反射的，您也可以
see why it's a little bit pain
看看为什么有点痛苦
all right if you had to convert all of
如果您必须转换所有
your configuration to that it's actually
您的配置实际上
I think easier to read when it's
我认为它更容易阅读
annotations I kind of prefer that so
我有点喜欢这样的注释
we're not ready to you know push people
我们还没有准备好让您知道推人
into functional being definitions for
进入功能存在的定义
everything but it's an interesting
一切，但这很有趣
option spring cloud function has some
选择弹簧云功能有一些
functional beam definition features it
功能光束定义功能
is really fast and it works really well
真的非常快而且效果很好
on constrained environments like AWS
在AWS等受限环境中
lambda for instance or example spring
例如lambda或春天
food spring cloud function I just
我只是食物春天的云功能
mentioned there's this microbe maps set
提到这里有微生物地图
of applications there are benchmarks in
的应用程序中有基准
there as well
还有
that's where the fun can bunk come from
那就是乐趣可以来自的地方
if you're interested in the source code
如果您对源代码感兴趣
and spring foo of course definitely
当然还有春季foo
worth mention another thing I looked at
值得一提的是我看过的另一件事
was what happens when you constrain the
当你约束
CPUs so this happens a lot these days
CPU，所以这几天经常发生
because people are running in
因为人们在奔跑
virtualized environments they're running
他们正在运行的虚拟环境
in Cuba Nettie's they're running in
在古巴Nettie，他们正在
containers that have got constrained
受到约束的容器
CPUs and we had this app from the Rif
CPU，我们从Rif获得了这个应用
project riff service platform which runs
运行的项目即兴服务平台
a function and with four CPUs they would
一个功能，并具有四个CPU
style in less than three seconds but if
在不到三秒钟的时间内样式化
he went to one CPU it went up to nearly
他去了一个CPU，它几乎增加了
17 second assassin horrible is really
17秒刺客真恐怖
horrible but the same exact app or the
糟糕，但完全相同的应用或
same features would run in six hundred
相同的功能将在600中运行
milliseconds before CPU and a thousand
CPU前一千毫秒
milliseconds in one CPU and the
一个CPU的毫秒数和
difference between the two is the
两者之间的区别是
original sucky one was Tomcat and auto
最初的烂货是Tomcat和auto
configuration and you know configuration
配置，你知道配置
or was that the the one that doesn't
还是那个不
suck is Nettie
烂是内蒂
so less fewer threads so less load on
更少的线程，更少的负载
the CPU
CPU
Nettie functional bean definitions but
Nettie功能Bean定义，但是
exactly the same features
完全相同的功能
so it's interesting there's definitely
所以很有意思的是
some mileage there and that's one of the
那里有一些里程，这是其中之一
most dramatic it results I've ever seen
我见过最戏剧性的结果
last slide so ahead of time compilation
最后一张幻灯片，所以提前编译
is coming LVM and generate native images
即将到来的LVM并生成本机映像
for Java applications including spring
适用于Java应用程序，包括spring
boot applications this is the bunk
启动应用程序，这是铺
application I'm showing here started in
我在这里显示的应用程序开始于
40 milliseconds so that's what you're
40毫秒，这就是您要的
looking at right it's not just a factor
看着正确不仅仅是一个因素
of 10 it's a factor of a hundred faster
十分之一的速度提高了一百倍
than you know raw JVM startup time
比您知道的原始JVM启动时间
that's the promise and we know we'll get
那是承诺，我们知道我们会得到
there we're pretty close now I think
我想我们现在很接近
with a large class of spring food
带有大量春季食品
applications downside you lose all sorts
应用程序的缺点是您将失去各种各样
of things debugging JMX manageability
调试JMX可管理性
dynamic compilation so the runtime
动态编译，因此运行时
optimizations are gone
优化不见了
garbage collection it doesn't happen so
垃圾收集不会发生，所以
they're simulating all of that stuff but
他们正在模拟所有这些东西，但是
they're basically you know that they're
他们基本上是你知道他们是
starting from a long way behind right
从很远的地方开始
there's a lot of engineering effort has
有很多工程上的努力
gone into the JVM over the years you're
这些年来，您进入了JVM
not going to be able to take advantage
无法利用
of that running this kind of application
运行这种应用程序的
many issues have been sold so we're
许多问题已经售出，所以我们
working quite closely with the Oracle
与Oracle紧密合作
team they want to bring out to work on
他们想带动的团队
growth year and we want them to work so
成长的一年，我们希望他们如此努力
it's still working progressed but I
它仍在工作，但我
think yogam was predicting spring 5.3
认为yogam预测春季5.3
might be a target for this I think
我认为这可能是目标
that's probably it's probably fairly
那可能是相当公平的
accurate it'll happen before that but
准确的会在那之前发生，但是
you know I don't even think that native
你知道我什至不认为那个本地人
images will be in production before that
图像将在此之前制作
anyway so that was the end a bunch of
无论如何，这就是一堆的结局
links there so you can take a picture
链接在那里，以便您可以拍照
I'll send the slides out anyway you can
我会尽量将幻灯片发送出去
all have a link to all the links at some
每个人都有一个指向所有链接的链接
point in the future so I've got to stop
指向未来，所以我必须停下来
there because it is time for beer
在那里，是时候喝啤酒了
I can ask answer questions over beer
我可以问啤酒问题
does that sound like a reasonable
听起来合理吗
compromise thank you
妥协谢谢
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]